Sidita Duli

Data Analyst

Mid-Level Data Analyst with 2 years of experience in data analysis projects, and a PhD in Parallel Programming of Weibull Distribution parameters.

Well-acquainted with SQL, Excel and Python. Different freelancing projects in SciPy, NumPy, matplotlib, and Pandas. Different certifications from Datacamp, Coursera.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancing platforms

Python Developer

October 2018 - Present

- Developed and debugged Python applications for 50+ clients, maintaining a high standard code, and customizing to the requirements.
- Prepared professional Jupyter Notebook with proper comments at each step.

AFDV Marketing, Ottawa, Canada

Data Analyst, Part-time, Remote

August 2022 - December 2022

- Analyzed SQL scripts and designed the solution to develop a custom ETL pipeline by using Python.
- Consumed APIs while utilizing Python requests to read and analyze numerous JSON reports.

Founder of the programming blog siditaduli.com

SEO Analyst

August 2015 - Present

- Collected and analyzed raw data to better understand search engine optimization efforts.
- Analyzed the Dashboard from tools: Google Analytics, Google Search Console, and Semrush.

internetpeople GmbH, Innsbruck, Austria

Software Developer, Part-time, Remote

December 2010 - December 2014

 Developed and maintained web application back-end components, using Java technologies.

University of Shkodra, Albania

Software Developer

October 2006 - May 2022

- Integrated *Python Programming* course in Bachelor of Computer Sciences, preparing course syllabus and lecturers.
- Researcher in Parallel Programming approach of Weibull Distribution Parameters estimation.

† Shkoder, Albania +355 69 26 44 356 siditaduli27@gmail.com

LINKS

WEBSITE LINKEDIN GITHUB

SKILLS

Python

SciPy NumPy Matplotlib Seaborn **Pandas** Excel SQL MySQL PostgreSQL Jupyter REST API Git / GitHub Docker products Google Analytics Google Cloud **BigQuery**

EDUCATION

SEO tools

University of Montenegro

Ph.D. in Parallel Programming

University of Tirana

MSc Computer Science

University of Shkodra

BS Computer Science

Foreign Languages

English Italian German

Mobility

University of Zagreb

Lecturer of Software Engineering